The authority meeting, get the invocation by Ms. Mary Jane Wailey.
Let us pray.
Heavenly Father, we come before you tonight asking for your guidance, wisdom, and support as we begin this meeting.
Help us to engage in meaningful discussion and nurture the bonds that bring us together.
Fill us with your grace as we make decisions that affect our community.
May our actions today serve the greater good through Jesus Christ our Lord. Amen.
Okay.
Number four, public input and ask individual appearances. We have none.
Number five, A claims list.
Motion approved.
Sorry.
Hi.
There are five B minutes from the February 3rd, 2026 regular meeting.
Motion approved.
Hi.
Number six in the other business, which has risen since the postings agenda, could not have been anticipated prior to the time of posting.
Number seven staff reports.
Number eight trustee community announcements.
Trust manage your communications number nine.
This time.
Okay.
Number 10, adjournment.
Motion.
Thank you.
Hi.
Sorry.
That's why we like it when you said.